Anthony F. C. Wallace Papers 1920-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.64a
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. Research Notes and Drafts, 23 lin. feet (Box 24-73)
  - A. Indian Research, 1947-1975; 4.5 linear feet
    Notes and drafts from Wallace's research among the Seneca and Tuscarora Indians. Materials include field notes, notes and photocopies from primary and secondary sources, and several issues of the Allegany Reservation newsletter Oh-Ho-Ye-Noh (1970-1972). Although restrictions exist on the Tuscarora Rorschach tests because of the sensitive personal information revealed, the series includes unrestricted censored versions and summary reports as well as the published work Modal Personality of the Tuscarora Indians as Revealed in the Rorschach Test.
    Correspondence that Wallace filed with his notes also appears in Series II A, which includes correspondence with local historian Merle H. Deardorff of the Warren County (Pa.) Historical Society. The Deardorff correspondence contains detailed descriptions of Iroquois (particularly Seneca) history and culture, with thorough discussions and analyses of the lives of Cornplanter, Handsome Lake, and Blacksnake, and other Indians of New York State and Pennsylvania.
    Related Indian materials appear in Subseries B, Revitalization and Culture; Series III, Bibliographic Notecards, which includes card files of primary and secondary source notes; Series XI, Photographs, which contains Indian reservation photographs taken by Wallace and his father, and in the Paul A.W. Wallace portion of the collection.
    - American Quarterly, 1979; 5 items
    - Conference on American Indian Collections, 1967; 69 items
    - Iroquois Field Trip, 1952 -- APS Grant Materials, 25 items
    - Beavers, 1962-1967; 28 items
    - Journal Excerpts, 1803-1823; 2 folders
    - Buffalo and Erie County Historical Society
    - Carlson, Liz, 1984; 39 items
    - Trip, July 3-9, 1952, 17 items
    - Miscellaneous papers, 1883; 21 items
    - Deardorff, Merle H., 1952-1968; 65 items
    - Ethnohistory of Diehl and Overpeck Sites
    - Notes
    - Printed Materials
    - Burton Historical Collection--Notes, 1819
    - Field notes:
      - Archaeology, Kintnersville, 1947, 37 items
      - Cold Spring, 16-31 August 1952, 13 items
      - Cold Spring, 20-26 October 1951 "Six Nations Meeting", 1 vol.
      - Cold Spring, 30 January-8 February 1952, 1 vol.
    - Miscellaneous Notes
    - Journal, 1760; 38 items
    - Henry Francis duPont Winterthur Museum, 1978-1979; 2 items
    - Tuscarora Myths (ca. 1888-1890), 1 vol.
    - Hunter Problem, The, 44 items
    - Iroquois Research Project, 54 items
    - Notes on [Chester County Historical Society], 1799-1878; 83 items
    - Sketch of the Manners, Customs, Religion, and Government of the Senecas in 1800, 31 items
    - Huron and Iroquois Materials [Notes], 4 items
    - Kinzua Dam, 1962; 17 items
    - Kirkland's Census of Iroquois [1789]
    - Journal, 1887; 16 items
    - Munsee Recitation Festival, n.d.; 7 items
    - Oh-he-yoh-noh Newsletter (Allegany Indian Reservation), 1972-1977; 5 folders
      - Folder 1, June 22, 1972-May 30, 1973; 25 items
      - Folder 2, June 6, 1973-January 4, 1974; 25 items
      - Folder 3, January 23, 1974-December 18, 1974; 37 items
      - Folder 4, January 8, 1975-November 5, 1975; 31 items
      - Folder 5, November 12, 1975-October 26, 1977; 33 items
    - December 1946, 1946-1947; 27 items
    - Parker, Arthur Caswell, 1881-1955, 1954; 3 items
    - Journal, 1 April-30 June 1760, 45 items
    - Draper Collection--Notes, 2 folders
    - Erie Triangle, n.d.; 1 vol.
    - Research Notes: American Indians, 2 folders
    - Research Notes: American Philosophical Society and Historical Society of Pennsylvania
    - History of Warren County, Pennsylvania
    - Seneca Pictorial Material
    - Visit to Cornplanter in 1798
    - State Historical Society of Wisconsin, 1953; 2 items
    - Journal excerpts and correspondence with Mary Jackson Shoemaker regarding Joel Sawyne
    - Wallace, Paul A.W., 1936-1947; 8 folders
      - Ethnological field notes, 1936-1947
      - Six Nations Journal, 1936
      - Six Nations Reserve: Hess, Jacob and Loft, William, 1936
      - Six Nations Reserve: Hess, Jacob, 1936
      - Six Nations Reserve: Loft, William Dewaseragech, Interview, 1937, 1942
      - Six Nations Reserve: Montour, Joseph F., 1936
      - Six Nations Reserve: Peters, Nichodemus, 1936
      - Six Nations Reserve: Williams, Isaiah, [1936]
    - Warren, Pennsylvania Centennial, 1897
    - Notes
    - Genealogical Gleanings of Siggins and Other Pennsylvania Families, 1918
    - Robert Morris
  - B. Revitalization and Culture, 1950-1970; 4.5 linear feet
    Notes and drafts from Wallace's research on revitalization movements, personality and culture, cognition and culture, and religion. Materials include handwritten notes, photocopies of primary and secondary sources, and componential analyses of linguistic terminology. Some material overlaps with that in Subseries A, Indian Research.
    - Right of Aesthetic Realism to be Known, 1975; 1 item
    - History of the St. Regis Reservation and several Iroquois pamphlets and drawings, c. 1948; 68 items
    - Puzzling Status of Brahman Priests in Hindu India, 1983; 10 items
    - Atkins, John, 2 folders
      - Componential Analysis Revisited and Memoranda, 40 items
      - Game Rules and the Rules of Culture (from Buchler, Ira and Hugo Nutini, ed., Game Theory in the the Behavioral Sciences, Ch. 11), 1969; 24 items
    - Psychoanalytic Observations of the Acculturation Process, 1954; 26 items
    - Movements of Total Transformation, 1972; 4 items
    - Becker, Marshall Joseph, 1990; 2 folders
      - Grant Proposal--Lenape Lives, 1990; 93 items
      - Origins of Trade Silver Among the Lenape, 1990; 6 items
    - Defense Mechanisms and Structure of the Total Personality, 1936; 17 items
    - Development and Problems of the Theory of the Instincts, 1936-1937; 26 items
    - Preliminary Evaluation of Librium (RO 5-0690) in the Treatment of Anxiety Reactions, n.d. (ca. 1959?); 22 items
    - Hallowell Symposium (American Anthropological Association), 1975; 114 items
    - Miscellaneous publications, 1954-1959; 40 items
    - Preliminary Evaluation of Librium (RO 5-0690) in the Treatment of Anxiety Reactions, n.d. (ca. 1959?); 22 items
    - Structure of Interpersonal Relations in Onondaga Society (M.A. Thesis, University of Pennsylvania), 1950; 49 items
    - Panculture: A Taxonomy from Murdock's Universal Basics (chapter from Bernardo Bernardi, ed., The Concepts and Dynamics of Culture, The Hague and Paris: Mouton Publishers), 1977; 28 items
    - Phenomenon of Religion Seen Scientifically: An Essay to Integrate a Multi-disciplinary Picture, 1971; 20 items
    - Natchez Social Structure, n.d.; 6 items
    - Campbell, Donald Thomas, 1916-, 2 folders
      - Evolutionary Theory in Social Science: A Reappraisal, 1961; 52 items
      - Some Contributions of Anthropology to Psychology and Some Psychological Comments on Anthropological Method, 1958; 30 items
    - Symposium on Genetic Psychology, 1952; 1 vol.
    - A Study in Nativism: The Red Scare of 1919-1920 (manuscript and published forms), 1964; 29 items
    - Binary Value Categories, 1960; 50 items
    - Publish or Perish: Negro Jehovah's Witness Cultural Adaptation in the Ghetto, 1970; 35 items
    - A Systematic Study of the Roles of Verbal Content and of Visual and Auditory Cues, 8 items
    - Game Rules and the Rules of Culture (from Buchler, Ira and Hugo Nutini, ed., Game Theory in the Behavioral Sciences, Ch. 11), 1969; 24 items
    - Denbrook Forge and Mill Sites: An Archaeological Study (M.A. Thesis, Drew University), 1980; 165 items
    - Cornplanter articles, 1941, 1970; 28 items
    - Adolescent Drug Use in Cross-Cultural Perspective, 1992; 9 items
    - Review of Eliade's work, possibly by AFCW and an unidentified excerpt, 9 items
    - Concept of Anomie, n.d.; 23 items
    - Fogelson, Raymond D., 4 folders
      - Atlantic City Fantasia, n.d.; 35 items
      - Cherokee Booger Mask Tradition, 1979; 38 items
      - Native North American Philosophy and World View, 1980; 37 items
      - Person, Self, and Identity: Some Anthropological Retrospects, Circumspects, and Prospects, 1982; 43 items
    - Jesters: Reflections on Anthropology and on Human Nature, 1976; 11 items
    - Aquarian New Age Community and Religion (two papers), 1971; 26 items
    - Gans, Herbert J., 1956-1957; 2 folders
      - Effects of Suburban New Town Life (proposal), 1957; 37 items
      - Human Implications of Current Redevelopment and Relocation Planning, 1956-1957; 57 items
    - Gradual and Quantum Changes in the History of Chuukese (Trukese) Phonology, 1992; 11 items
    - Management Lessons from the Industrial Revolution: A Comparative Study of Industrial Innovation in England and France, 1066-1850, 1984; 7 items
    - Adolescent Drug Use in Cross-Cultural Perspective, 1992; 9 items
    - An Ethnological report on the Historic Habitat of the Sauk, Fox, and Iowa Indians (from Docket 158, Indian Claims Commission), 1955; 62 items
    - Who's Cooking? A Group Model of Auto-Culinary Practices, n.d.; 29 items
    - Review of Pierre Teilhard de Chardin's The Phenomenon of Man, 1952; 2 items
    - Interview with "Rita," Southwest Philadelphia resident and mother of a biracial child (draft and final copy), 1960; 40 items
    - Philadelphia Psychoanalytic Institute, 1932; 19 items
    - Ethnohistory and Alcohol Studies, 1984; 13 items
    - S.D.S. as a Revitalization Movement, 1969; 25 items
    - Correspondence, 1970; 3 items
    - On the General Applicability of Revitalization Theory, 1972; 112 items
    - Operational Definition of Values (special supplement in the American Behavioral Scientist), 1962; 2 vols.
    - Equivalence Structures and the Organization of Diversity, 1971; 8 items
    - A Map of 18th Century Indian Towns in Pennsylvania, 26 items
    - Correspondence and notes regarding psychiatric hospitals in England, 1955; 70 items
    - Publications, 1979-1991; 60 items
    - Zur Genese des Maskenwesens im ostlichen Waldland Nordamerikas (in Deutsch), 1975; 73 items
    - Economic Analysis of Natural Hazards: An Ordered Choice Approach, 1973; 28 items
    - Clinical Evaluation of Psychostimulants, 1959; 7 items
    - Millenarian Movements and Resocialization, 1972; 12 items
    - Projective Techniques and their Cross-Cultural Application (three chapters), 2 folders
      - Folder 1, n.d.; 116 items
      - Folder 2, n.d.; 104 items
    - Nativistic Movements (review of article, probably by AFCW), 1943; 5 items
    - Letters from Edward Sapir, 1965; 79 items
    - Diagnostic Criteria--The Concept of Normal and Abnormal and notes by AFCW, 1941; 13 items
    - Mahler, Margaret S., 1967-1968; 2 folders
      - Observations on Adaptation and Defense In Statu Nascendi, 1968; 11 items
      - On Human Symbiosis and the Vicissitudes of Individuation, 1967; 12 items
    - Projective Psychological Findings in Palau Personality (notes), 4 items
    - A Theory of Metamotivation: The Biological Rooting of the Value-Life, 1967
    - Revitalization Movements: Theory and Practice as Evidenced among the Buddhists of Marahashtra, India, 21 items
    - Home-Centered Treatment of the Social Network of Schizophrenic Families: Two Approaches, ca. 1967; 16 items
    - Synthetic Function of the Ego, 1929; 16 items
    - Social Network of the Family of a Schizophrenic: Implications for Social and Preventive Psychology, 16 items
    - Infant Care and Personality (reversed image photostat and notes), 1959; 54 items
    - On Being Mad (includes six page letter from Osmond), 1952, 1966; 10 items
    - A Map of 18th Century Indian Towns in Pennsylvania, 26 items
    - Publications on Drugs, Psychoses, and Schizophrenia, 1953-1956; 41 items
    - Publications on Osksapmin people, 7 items
    - Social Rehabilitation of the Chronic Mental Patient, 1961; 46 items
    - Publications on Schizophrenia, 1949-1962; 30 items
    - Clinical Evaluation of Psychostimulants, 1959; 7 items
    - Publications on Culture, 1956-1958; 40 items
    - Role of Disorder in Human Activity and Thought (apparently chapter 8 of a larger text), 28 items
    - Child Development and the Dwelling Unit, 1957; 17 items
    - Nature of a Theoretical Natural Science of Society and notes on Radcliffe-Brown, 1948, n.d.; 134 items
    - Publications on Cognition and Culture, 1959-1963; 109 items
    - Analysis of Highland Amhara Personality Organization by Means of the Rorschach Test and Ethnographic Information, 1975; 25 items
    - Worte eines Seneca (Staat New York), 1973; 15 items
    - A Map of 18th Century Indian Towns in Pennsylvania, 26 items
    - Freud and Reich (review of Higgins, Mary and Chester M. Raphael's Reich Speaks of Freud), 1968; 2 items
    - Psychology of the Inventor (notes), n.d.; 4 items
    - Publications on Psychoses, 1956-1962; 77 items
    - To Observe the Response of Socially Crippled Patients to a Resocialization Program of Functional Social Work Intervention, 1963; 29 items
    - Psychological Anthropology: A Case Study in Culture Blindness?, 1974; 12 items
    - Papers on Indian Conversion, 1978; 47 items
    - Impact of an Innovative Treatment Program on the Structure and Culture of a Large State Mental Hospital, 1961; 46 items
    - A Logical and Cultural Analysis of Hallucinatory Sense-Experience, 1956; 4 items
    - Speck, Ross V., 2 folders
      - Home-Centered Treatment of the Social Network of Schizophrenic Families: Two Approaches, ca. 1967; 16 items
      - Social Network of the Family of a Schizophrenic: Implications for Social and Preventive Psychiatry, 16 items
    - American Indian Personality Types and their Sociocultural Roots, 52 items
    - American Indian Personality Types and their Sociocultural Roots, 52 items
    - Ecology in perspective: The human context of ecological research. In International Social Science Journal, vol. XXXIV, no. 3 (see printed materials catalog), 1982
    - Peyote Religion and the Ghost Dance, 1972; 4 items
    - Reprints on Gender Identity and Transsexualism, 1959-1968; 68 items
    - Notes and bibliographies, ca. 1970; 40 items
    - Notes, n.d.; 102 items
    - Beginnings, Endings, and New Endings in North American Indian Mythology, 1979; 13 items
    - Notes on the Psychoanalytic Significance of the Choice of Analyst
    - Tobin, Joseph M., 2 folders
      - Clinical Evaluation of Psychostimulants, 1959; 7 items
      - Preliminary Evaluation of Librium (RO 5-0690) in the Treatment of Anxiety Reactions, n.d. (ca. 1959?); 22 items
    - Principle of Multiple Function: Observations on Over-Determination, 1936, 1952; 11 items
    - Wallace, Anthony F. C., 1923-, 2 folders
      - Myth Analysis (aborted Culture and Personality project), ca. 100 items
      - Papers on Wallace by University of Minnesota students, 1965; 64 items
    - Revitalization: The Songs of the Sixties, 1969; 77 items
    - Women's Status and Career Patterns materials, 1969; 42 items
    - Witthoft, John, 2 folders
      - Miscellaneous articles, 1950-1967; 4 items
      - Technology of the Calico Site, n.d.; 17 items
    - Waiting for Deliverance, n.d.; 12 items
    - Ch' u an-chen: A Revitalization Movement in North China During the 12th and 13th Centuries, 8 items
    - Cultural Integration of the Hallucinatory Experience--The Use of Peyote within the Native American Culture, 1971; 22 items
  - C. Technology and Culture, 1970-1995; 3 linear feet
    Notes and drafts relating to Wallace's study of technological innovation and its interaction with social and cultural change. Materials include handwritten notes, photocopies of primary and secondary sources, and several papers from conferences and talks on technology and social change.
    - Talk--Seminar on Culture and Technology, 1987; 54 items
    - Changing Worlds, 22 folders
      - Agents, 1976-1978; 4 items
      - Anthropology Text ("Team Text")--Correspondence, 1969-1971; 18 items
      - Bibliography, n.d.; 1 vol.
      - Board of Trustees Talk, 1962; 2 items
      - Chapter 1--Nature of Culture, ca. 1969; 88 items
      - Chapter 2--Revisions, ca. 1969; 17 items
      - Chapter 2--Surviving Hunters and Gatherers, ca. 1969; 44 items
      - Chapter 3--The Village Farmers and Herdsmen, ca. 1969; 35 items
      - Chapter 4--The Cantonal System, ca. 1969; 21 items
      - Chapter 5--The Classical States, ca. 1969; 46 items
      - Chapter 5B--The Industrial Revolution, ca. 1969; 62 items
      - Chapter 6--The Nature of Man, ca. 1969; 12 items
      - Expenses
      - Introduction to Cultural Text Project, ca. 1969; 7 items
      - Manuscript--Chapters 1-3, 1978; 248 items
      - Manuscript--Chapters 4-Notes, 1978; 224 items
      - Preface, n.d.; 1 item
      - Prospectus, ca. 1969; 6 items
      - Publishers, 1976-1977; 21 items
      - Reviews by Random House Readers, 1979; 22 items
      - Revisions after September 15, 1978, ca. 1978; 8 items
      - Table of Contents, ca. 1969; 5 items
    - Central European Mining Information, 1979-1980; 42 items
    - Jeremy, David J., 1973-1986; 2 folders
      - Articles on Technology Transmission, 1973-1981; 79 items
      - Articles on Textile Technology and Workers, 1973-1986; 34 items
    - Fellowship, 1978; 54 items
    - Neolithic Period--Southern and Eastern Europe, 1977; 5 items
    - Mellon Seminar, 1985-1988
      - Administrative Materials, 1986; 154 items
      - Commentaries by a Few, 1987; 30 items
      - Rethinking Technology and Culture, 1985; 131 items
      - Technology and Culture Notes, 1987-1988; 134 items
    - Mechanical Revolution: Inventors' name list (aborted project), ca. 1978; 62 items
    - Notes, n.d.; 3 items
    - Polgar, Katherine, 1979; 4 items
    - Princeton University Press, 1979-1985; 142 items
    - Technology and Culture Seminars, 1988-1990; 4 folders
    - Social Context of Innovation, 17 folders
      - "Front Matter", 1 item
      - Book Reviews, 1981-1984; 35 items
      - Chapter I--The Challenge, n.d.; 6 items
      - Chapter IA--Steam, n.d.; 42 items
      - Chapter II--The First Responses, n.d.; 24 items
      - Chapter IIA--Iron, n.d.; 15 items
      - Chapter III--The Gentlemen of Atlantis, n.d.; 11 items
      - Chapter IIIA--Coal, 64 items
      - Chapter IV--The Tradesmen, n.d.; 9 items
      - Chapter V--The Mechanicians, n.d.; 4 items
      - Idea/Inventor Sequences--Charts, n.d.; 7 items
      - Industrial Revolution as Evolutionary Event, 2 items
      - Introduction, n.d.; 2 folders; 42 items
      - Inventors--Outline, n.d.; 23 items
      - The Conquest of the World, n.d.; 9 items
      - Theory of Culture, n.d.; 1 item
    - Myth of Flawed Creation (handwritten manuscript), 77 items
    - Text Plan, 1969; 45 items
  - D. Rockdale, 1971-1995; 8 linear feet
    Materials from Anthony F.C. Wallace's research on the Rockdale area of Delaware County, Pennsylvania, particularly with regard to its mills and industries, but also including extensive information on well known families such as the Smiths and du Ponts. The Rockdale subseries includes notes, extensive photocopies of primary and secondary sources, papers from conferences and talks on Rockdale, Delaware County, and industrialization, student seminar papers related to industrialization and Delaware County history, and the original handwritten manuscript of Rockdale.
    A unique item also appears with the Rockdale materials: an original 19th century account book from the Sharpless-Worrall company, which apparently supplied mills with raw materials and equipment. Several familiar Delaware County names such as Lammot, Pennell, Willcox, and others appear in the book.
    Series III, Notecards, contains information on bibliographic sources for Rockdale and census data on Rockdale area families. Series XI, Photographs contains over 300 photographs and over 3000 slides of textile mills and machinery and the Rockdale area, a dream collection for historians of industrialization and Delaware County.
    - Subseries 1. Primary Source notes
      - Haines Collection, 10 items
      - Phillips Collection (notes), 22 items
      - Notes, 9 items
      - Publications list (photocopies), 43 items
      - Lammot, Daniel--Lenni Mill Lease, 5 items
      - Sellers Genealogy (notes), 5 items
      - Sellers Family Poetry, 8 items
      - Sellers, George Escol--Personal Recollections of Coleman Sellers by his son George Escol Sellers, 63 items
      - Peale-Sellers Papers (notes), 55 items
      - Ord, George--Papers (notes), 3 items
      - Maclure, William--Papers (notes), 5 items
      - Sellers, George Escol--Personal Recollections of Nathan Sellers, 26 items
      - Hill, Peter-- Business (notes and photocopies), 35 items
      - Dutton, Thomas (photocopies), 37 items
      - Crozer, John P. (notes), 3 items
      - Broomall, John M. (notes), 1 item
      - Martin, William--Machinery List, 1 item
      - Sellers Papers (photocopies), 1824-1831; 115 items
      - Sellers Papers (photocopies), 1824-1851; 132 items
      - London Cooperative Society Constitution, 1825; 6 items
      - Sellers, Anne--Diary (notes and photocopy), 1828, 1830; 18 items
      - Phillips, John S.--Letter from L. Lederer, 1841; 1 item
      - Bache, Alexander Dallas to John P. Crozier (transcription), 1844; 2 items
      - Miscellaneous, 1973, 1978; 15 items
      - Account Books of Manufacturers (notes), 19 items
      - Miscellaneous Notes, 11 items
      - Dun and Bradstreet manuscripts (notes and photocopies), 1852-1888; 37 items
      - Ronaldson, James to Jonathan Russell, 1822; 4 items
      - Church records (notes), 43 items
      - Congregation of Calvary Protestant Episcopal Church, 20 items
      - Miscellaneous Notes on Sources, 36 items
      - Darlington, William--Ledger "A" (photocopies), 1804-1809; 3 items
      - Valley Forge Commune, Latta Family (notes and photocopies), 1814-1890; 10 items
      - Darlington, Edward--Letters (notes and photocopies), 1830-1865; 23 items
      - Townsend, Washington--On Marriage (notes and photocopies), 1847; 6 items
      - Lammot, Daniel (notes and photocopies), 1849, 1852; 4 items
      - Medical Reporter (notes), 1853-; 9 items
      - Hill, Peter (notes and photocopies), 1855,1858; 5 items
      - Riddle, Samuel--Letter (photocopy), 1871; 2 items
      - Morley, Christine C.--Types of Early Mills in Delaware County, and their Use of Water Power, 1953; 13 items
      - Pennell, Hannah--Will (1836), 7 items
      - Tax Assessments (notes), 10 items
      - Blakely, Theodore and Miscellaneous Blakely Records, 11 items
      - Pusey's Mill, 1730; 1 item
      - Phillips, John S.--Lease, 1825; 4 items
      - Wills (transcripts), 1828-1926; 102 items
      - Tax Assessments II, 1829-1859; ca. 75 items
      - Tax Assessments I, 1829-1859; ca. 75 items
      - Strike Conspirators' Tax Assessments, 1829-1860, 1894; 19 items
      - Poor Children's Names, 1829; 12 items
      - Deeds--Smith, Richard S., 1832-1875; 8 items
      - Riddle Papers (notes and photocopies), 1835-1972; 24 items
      - Conspiracy Trial, 1842; 7 items
      - Smith, Richard S.--Deed,Old Sable Works, 1845; 6 items
      - Crozer, John P.--Will and Related Documents, 1866-1870; 35 items
      - Riddle, Samuel--Will, 1888; 18 items
      - Latter Day Saints Microfilm--Delaware County Records (notes and correspondence), 1971; 15 items
      - Dutton Papers (notes), 1 item
      - County Tax Records, 11 items
      - Broomall, John, 2 items
      - Glen Riddle Mills, Parkmount Mills, ca. 20 items
      - Leiper, Thomas--Collection, 5 items
      - Post-Boy newspaper (notes), 3 items
      - Miscellaneous notes, 42 items
      - Baker Notebooks (notes), 1 item
      - Glen Mills Paper Mills, Sarum Forge, 1759-1939; 4 items